James Kolbe Papers, 1958-2006 (bulk 1985-2006)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 2: Congressional Activities, 1980-2006
  - Speeches, Series 4: 1981-2006
    - Casa de los Niños, May 2, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 95)
    - Job Corp, May 2, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 96)
    - Remarks, Arizona-Mexico Trade and Investment Forum, May 5, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 97)
    - Remarks, Israeli Memorial Ceremony, May 5, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 98)
    - Remarks, Annual National Guard Association of Arizona Conference banquet, May 17, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Medicare Modernization and Prescription Drugs: Meaningful Change and Real Responsibility, August, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Sonoita Rotary, August 7, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Cochise County Mayor's Administrators, August 8, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Southern Arizona Contractors Association, August 8, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Remarks, America Israel Friendship League 2003 Partners in Democracy dinner, September 14, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - GTEC talking points, September 15, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Remarks, terminal opening at Tucson International Airport, October 28, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Talking points, VFW and Auxiliary Quarterly meeting, November 1, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Talking points, Air National Guard Awards ceremony, November 2, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Briefing on trade, manufacturing and the economy, November 19, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Tribute to Chuck Anderson of Raytheon, December 8, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Graduate Club, December 9, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Catalina Stewardship Sunday, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Draft remarks to University of Arizona Conference, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Southern Arizona Leadership Council, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - Remark, Phoenix Chapter of Council on Foreign Relations, January 7, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - Sierra Vista Rotary, January 12, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 18)
    - J-net, January 13, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 19)
    - Keynote speech, Tucson Feria Educativa, March 6, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 20)
    - Talking points, Young Lawyers Division of Pima County Bar, March 6, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 21)
    - Talking points, defense budget, March, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 22)
    - State of the District, April 7, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 23)
    - McCain-Kolbe Press Conference, April 22, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 24)
    - Talking points, Congressional art competition ceremony, April 25, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 25)
    - Greater Tucson Leadership, April 30, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 26)
    - Luxembourg American Cemetery, May 31, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 27)
    - Environmental Protection Agency/Caterpillar Clean School Bus Partnership, June 3, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 28)
    - Naturalization ceremony, July 1, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 29)
    - Welcome remarks, Green Vally Town Hall, July 2, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 30)
    - Southern Arizona Association of Health Underwriters, August 10, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 31)
    - South of 45 Breakfast Club, August 12, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 32)
    - Tucson Sunrise Rotary, August 12, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 33)
    - Pima County College All College Day, August 13, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 34)
    - Southern Arizona Mortgage Lenders, August 17, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 35)
    - University of Arizona Medical College, August 26, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 36)
    - Joe Haro: Bronze Star Award ceremony, August 28, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 37)
    - Export Achievement Award, Breault talking points, September 1, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 38)
    - Rincon Rotary, September 1, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 39)
    - Red Cross event: Save a Life Saturday: Together we Prepare, September 10, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 40)
    - 1200 Club, September 10, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 41)
    - Evergreen Cemetery and candlelight vigil, September 11, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 42)
    - Introductory remarks, Council on Foreign Relations meeting with Alvaro Uribe, President of Columbia, September 24, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 43)
    - Cardiology conference, October 2, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 44)
    - Fast Lane Project at Border Port of Entry, October 4, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 45)
    - Temple Anshei Israel, October 14, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 46)
    - American Association of Retired Persons, October 15, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 47)
    - Western Army National Guard Aviation Training Site remarks, October 15, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 48)
    - Opening statement at Drug Free Communities press conference, October 18, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 49)
    - University of Arizona civic engagement, October 18, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 50)
    - Job Corp education event with Tom Horne, October 19, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 51)
    - World Care event, October 19, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 52)
    - Remarks, Raytheon, October 21, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 53)
    - Sunbelt World Trade, October 25, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 54)
    - Draft remarks, Arizona CFR, October 27, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 55)
    - Saguaro Business Club, October 27, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 56)
    - Business Development Finance Corporation, October 27, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 57)
    - GTEC, October 28, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 58)
    - Talking points, Roadrunner Civitan Club, November 2, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 59)
    - Detailed provisions in Kolbe-Stenholm Social Security Reform Bill, November 14, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 60)
    - Andean Talks: Inside Tucson Business, November 29, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 61)
    - Social Security Reform, November 29, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 62)
    - Remarks, Andean Country members of Parliament, November 30, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 63)
    - New York Times Social Security Reform, December 1, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 64)
    - FLIR, December 9, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 65)
    - Cochise County Mayor/Managers Luncheon, December 15, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 66)
    - Center for Academic Success High School graduation, December 16, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 67)
    - Bush-Kerry post debate analysis, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 68)
    - Remarks, Coldwell Bankers, February 14, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 69)
    - Remarks, Republican Main Street Partnership Meeting, February 17, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 70)
    - Talking points, Spectraphysics All Hands ISO Celebration, February 18, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 71)
    - Talking points, EOS Technologies Ribbon cutting, February 19, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 72)
    - Social Security Reform, Cochise College, February 22, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 73)
    - Thunder Mountain Republican Women, February 22, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 74)
    - Remarks, Women in Business, February 23, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 75)
    - Sierra Vista Chamber, February 23, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 76)
    - Remarks, Piper Rudnick Meeting, March 1, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 77)
    - Remarks, Baker/Hostetler Tax, Budget and Legislative Policy Seminar, March 16, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 78)
    - Remarks, Vista del Rio Cultural Resource Park, March 19, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 79)
    - Prosperity through Security and Choice, Federal Issues Forum, March 23, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 80)
    - University of Arizona Social Security Town Hall, April 29, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 81)
    - Voices Celebration, May 7, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 82)
    - HaShoah, May 8, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 83)
    - Holocaust ceremony, May 8, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 84)
    - Let Freedom Sing, July 4, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 85)
    - Marine Corps League, July 7, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 86)
    - Sierra Vista Rotary Club, July 7, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 87)
    - A Perspective on the Sudan, Catalina United Methodist Church, July 10, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 88)
    - Remarks, "Supporting Our Troops", Voters for New Global Policies, July 12, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 89)
    - Arizona-Mexico Commission, July 18, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 90)
    - Legislative update talking points, Pima County Republican Club, August 2, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 91)
    - Talking points, Legislative update, August 9, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 92)
    - Remarks, National Association of Purchasing Management, August 9, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 93)
    - Introduction for Secretary Mike Leavitt, August 10, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 94)
    - Tucson Retired/Enlisted Association remarks, August 10, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 95)
    - Talking points for RFID test announcement, August 11, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 96)
    - UMC Trauma Center expansion, August 13, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 97)
    - Arizona-Mexico Commission, August, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 98)
    - Legislative update talking points, August, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 99)
    - United Nations Southern Arizona Association, August, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 100)
    - Remarks, Corporacion Andina De Fomento Conference, Conference on Trade and Investment in the Americas, September 7, 2005-September 8, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 101)
    - Oro Valley Republican Women Club, September 9, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 102)
    - National Association of Conservation Districts, September 12, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Talking points, Border Patrol Check presentation event, October 4, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Reflections on 22 Years in Congress, Yale Club, October 6, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Tucson Interfaith HIV/AIDS network, October 23, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Movement on Immigration reform bill update, October 27, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Chinese Cultural Center opening, October 29, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - University of Arizona dining in, November 19, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Keynote Address, NGO Watch, American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research, December 7, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Talking points, Business Coalition for Capacity Building, December 7, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Casas Adobe Rotary Club, December 21, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Gay and Lesbian Leadership Institute script, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Keynote Address, Lifetime Achievement Award for Robert Matsui, Washington International Trade Association Awards Dinner, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - State of the District, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Talking points, Congressional term limits, January 3, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - PCRC, January 17, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Remarks, Foothills Republican Women, January 17, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - Tucson's Australians/New Zealanders Club, January 18, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - Global Health: The Future and the Present, University Coalitions for Global Health, January 21, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - American Electronics Association meeting, February 6, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 19)
    - Remarks, United States Trade and Development Agency Country of the Year Award, February 14, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 20)
    - Remarks, CSIS/Global Health Dialogue, Paris, France, March 12, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 21)
    - Remarks, Council of the Americas Dinner, March 29, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 22)
    - Tucson Orthopedic Society, April 18, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 23)
    - Talking points, St. Phillips in the Foothills Church, April 19, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 24)
    - Foreign Policy Issues Update, Phoenix Committee on Foreign Relations, April 20, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 25)
    - Remarks, United States Global Leadership Campaign, April 20, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 26)
    - Talking points, Impact of Increasingly Globalized World, Eller College of Management, April 21, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 27)
    - Talking points, Building Dedication for United States Arid Land Agricultural Research Center, April 24, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 28)
    - Talking points, Migration and Trade, Washington International Trade Association, April 27, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 29)
    - Global Poverty Fight: An American Perspective, Development Executive Group, April 28, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 30)
    - Upon Receiving the President Ronald Reagan Memorial Award, 2006 Log Cabin Republicans National Dinner, April 29, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 31)
    - Commencement, Embry-Riddle Aeronautical University, May 6, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 32)
    - State of the District Address, Federal Issues Forum, May 8, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 33)
    - Talking points, The Humane Society of Southern Arizona, May 11, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 34)
    - Talking points, Border Trade Alliance, May 12, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 35)
    - Commencement, University of Arizona, May 13, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 36)
    - Award Dinner, Society for International Development, May 24, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 37)
    - Page Graduation, Departure Ceremony, Cannon House Office Building, June 9, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 38)
    - Talking points, Perspective on Unmanned Aerial Vehicles, American Institute of Engineers, September 20, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 39)
    - Remarks, Social Security, Tucson Rotary Club, October 4, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 40)
    - Keynote speech, Log Cabin Dallas 10th Annual Grand Ol' Party, October 21, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 41)
    - Remarks, Eller International Business Environment Class, October 25, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 42)
    - International Trade: Removal of Barriers in the Age of Outsourcing, Eller College of Management (International Management Class), October 26, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 43)
    - Talking points, ISSS-ISAC Conference, October 27, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 44)
    - Remarks, Global AIDS Funding, University of Arizona, November 22, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 45)
    - Talking points, Council of State Governments, December 1, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 46)
    - Keynote remarks, Society for Mining Metallurgy and Exploration, December 11, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 47)
    - Thunderbird commencement address, Glendale, Arizona, December 15, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 48)
    - State of the District, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 49)
    - 99th Town Hall, undated (Box 122, Folder 50)
    - America Leads on Trade, Cannon 210, undated (Box 122, Folder 51)
    - Communal Areas Management Program for Indigenous Resources, undated (Box 122, Folder 52)
    - Congress Turn to Jump Start Free Trade, undated (Box 122, Folder 53)
    - Copper Caucus, undated (Box 122, Folder 54)
    - Draft Talking points, Arizona-Sonora Border Issues, undated (Box 122, Folder 55)
    - Fast Track: Economic Growth, undated (Box 122, Folder 56)
    - Free Trade talking points, undated (Box 122, Folder 57)
    - Getting Involved, Visit to Housing and Urban Development, undated (Box 122, Folder 58)
    - Miscellaneous Speeches, undated (Box 122, Folder 59)
    - Op-ed Response to Republic Anti-Maquila Articles, undated (Box 122, Folder 60)
    - Prayer Breakfast, undated (Box 122, Folder 61)
    - Public Policy Impact of September 11th, undated (Box 122, Folder 62)
    - Remarks, Arizona-Mexico Commission, undated (Box 122, Folder 63)
    - Remarks, Sallie Mae Event, undated (Box 122, Folder 64)
    - Remarks, Town Hall on Drug Problems, undated (Box 122, Folder 65)
    - Script, Children's Miracle Network Telethon, undated (Box 122, Folder 66)
    - Software Lumber Issue, Lumber Dealers Trade, undated (Box 122, Folder 67)
    - Statement, United States-Israel relations, undated (Box 122, Folder 68)
    - Statement, United States-Mexican Trade Relations/Relating to cement imports, Charles Pine of Charles W. Pine Associates and Kaibab Industries, undated (Box 122, Folder 69)
    - Talking points, ABC Initiative, Asa Hutchison's Arizona visit, undated (Box 122, Folder 70)
    - Talking points, BBC Call, undated (Box 122, Folder 71)
    - Talking points, Beyond Revisionism Focus on Investment, "Cost Protectionism", undated (Box 122, Folder 72)
    - Talking points, Regarding Why We Need Insurance Restructuring, undated (Box 122, Folder 73)
    - Terrorism, undated (Box 122, Folder 74)
  - Series 5: Office Files, 1985-2006
    This series contains schedules and event and travel itineraries and correspondence.
    - Schedules, 1986-2006
      This subseries contains daily schedules, appointments books and congressional meetings schedules. It is arranged chronologically.
      - Appointment book, 1986 (Box 122, Folder 75)
      - January, 1987-June, 1987 (Box 122, Folder 76)
      - July, 1987-December, 1987 (Box 122, Folder 77)
      - Town Hall and Speech Schedules, February, 1987-March, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 78)
      - Appointment book, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - January, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - February, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - March, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - April, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - May, 1988-June, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - July, 1988-August, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 7)
      - September, 1988-October, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 8)
      - November, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 9)
      - December, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 10)
      - Appointment book, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 11)
      - Congressional meetings, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 12)
      - Congressional meetings, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 13)
      - January, 1989-February, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 14)
      - March, 1989-May, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - June, 1989-September, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - October, 1989-December, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 3)
      - Appointment book, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - January, 1990-February, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 5)
      - March, 1990-May, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - June, 1990-August, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 7)
      - September, 1990-October, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 8)
      - November, 1990-December, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 9)
      - Appointment book, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 10)
      - Congressional meetings, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 11)
      - January, 1991-February, 1991 (Box 124, Folder 12)
      - March, 1991-April, 1991 (Box 124, Folder 13)
      - May, 1991-July, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - August, 1991-September, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - October, 1991-November, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - December, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - Appointment book, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - Congressional meetings, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - January, 1992-February, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 7)
      - March, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 8)
      - April, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 9)
      - May, 1992-June, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 10)
      - July, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 11)
      - August, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 12)
      - August, 1992-September, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 13)
      - October, 1992 (1 of 2) (Box 125, Folder 14)
      - October, 1992 (2 of 2) (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - November, 1992 (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - December, 1992 (Box 126, Folder 3)
      - Appointment book, 1992 (Box 126, Folder 4)
      - Congressional meetings, 1992 (Box 126, Folder 5)
      - January, 1993-February, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 6)
      - March, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 7)
      - April, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 8)
      - May, 1993-June, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 9)
      - July, 1993-August, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 10)
      - September, 1993-October, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 11)
      - November, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 12)
      - December, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 13)
      - Appointment book, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 14)
      - Congressional meetings, January, 1993-May, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 15)
      - Congressional meetings, June, 1993-December, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 16)
      - Public Events, 1993 (Box 127, Folder 1)
      - January, 1994-February, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 2)
      - March, 1994-April, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 3)
      - May, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 4)
      - June, 1994-July, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 5)
      - August, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 6)
      - September, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 7)
      - October, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 8)
      - November, 1994-December, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 9)
      - Appointment book, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - Congressional meetings, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 11)
      - January, 1995-June, 1995 (Box 127, Folder 12)
      - July, 1995-December, 1995 (Box 127, Folder 13)
      - January, 1995-March, 1995 (Box 127, Folder 14)
      - April, 1995-May, 1995 (Box 128, Folder 1)
      - June, 1995-July, 1995 (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - August, 1995 (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - September, 1995-October, 1995 (Box 128, Folder 4)
      - November, 1995-December, 1995 (Box 128, Folder 5)
      - Congressional meetings (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 128, Folder 6)
      - Congressional meetings (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - January, 1996-May, 1996 (Box 128, Folder 8)
      - June, 1996-December, 1996 (Box 128, Folder 9)
      - January, 1996 (Box 128, Folder 10)
      - February, 1996 (Box 128, Folder 11)
      - March, 1996-April, 1996 (Box 128, Folder 12)
      - May, 1996-June, 1996 (Box 128, Folder 13)
      - July, 1996-August, 1996 (Box 128, Folder 14)
      - September, 1996 (Box 128, Folder 15)
      - October, 1996 (Box 129, Folder 1)
      - November, 1996-December, 1996 (Box 129, Folder 2)
      - January, 1997-February, 1997 (Box 129, Folder 3)
      - March, 1997-April, 1997 (Box 129, Folder 4)
      - May, 1997-June, 1997 (Box 129, Folder 5)
      - July, 1997-August, 1997 (Box 129, Folder 6)
      - September, 1997 (Box 129, Folder 7)
      - October, 1997 (Box 129, Folder 8)
      - November, 1997-December, 1997 (Box 129, Folder 9)
      - Appointment book (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 129, Folder 10)
      - Appointment book (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 129, Folder 11)
      - Meeting requests, 1997 (Box 129, Folder 12)
      - United States House of Representatives Office of the Majority Whip Vote Schedule and District Work periods, 1997 (Box 129, Folder 13)
      - January, 1998-February, 1998 (Box 129, Folder 14)
      - March, 1998-April, 1998 (Box 129, Folder 15)
      - May, 1998-June, 1998 (Box 130, Folder 1)
      - July, 1998-August, 1998 (Box 130, Folder 2)
      - September, 1998 (Box 130, Folder 3)
      - October, 1998 (Box 130, Folder 4)
      - November, 1998-December, 1998 (Box 130, Folder 5)
      - Meeting requests (1 of 3), 1998 (Box 130, Folder 6)
      - Meeting requests (2 of 3), 1998 (Box 130, Folder 7)
      - Meeting requests (3 of 3), 1998 (Box 130, Folder 8)
      - January, 1999-February, 1999 (Box 130, Folder 9)
      - March, 1999-April, 1999 (Box 130, Folder 10)
      - May, 1999-June, 1999 (Box 130, Folder 11)
      - July, 1999-August, 1999 (Box 130, Folder 12)
      - September, 1999 (Box 131, Folder 1)
      - October, 1999 (Box 131, Folder 2)
      - November, 1999 (Box 131, Folder 3)
      - December, 1999 (Box 131, Folder 4)
      - Meeting requests, 1999 (Box 131, Folder 5)
      - January, 2000 (Box 131, Folder 6)
      - February, 2000 (Box 131, Folder 7)
      - March, 2000 (Box 131, Folder 8)
      - April, 2000 (Box 131, Folder 9)
      - May, 2000-June, 2000 (Box 131, Folder 10)
      - July, 2000 (Box 131, Folder 11)
      - August, 2000 (Box 131, Folder 12)
      - September, 2000 (Box 131, Folder 13)
      - October, 2000 (Box 131, Folder 14)
      - November, 2000-December, 2000 (Box 131, Folder 15)
      - Meeting requests, 2000 (Box 131, Folder 16)
      - January, 2001-February, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 1)
      - March, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 2)
      - April, 2001-May, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 3)
      - June, 2001-July, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 4)
      - August, 2001-September, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 5)
      - October, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 6)
      - November, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 7)
      - December, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 8)
      - January, 2002-February, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 9)
      - March, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 10)
      - April, 2002-May, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 11)
      - June, 2002-July, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 12)
      - August, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 13)
      - September, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 14)
      - October, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 15)
      - November, 2002-December, 2002 (Box 133, Folder 1)
      - Meeting requests, 2002 (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - January, 2003-March, 2003 (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - April, 2003 (Box 133, Folder 4)
      - May, 2003-July, 2003 (Box 133, Folder 5)
      - August, 2003-September, 2003 (Box 133, Folder 6)
      - October, 2003 (Box 133, Folder 7)
      - November, 2003-December, 2003 (Box 133, Folder 8)